#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jaskirat-kaur-805069a0 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Marketing
Digital Marketing
Fashion Blogging

## Languages

Hindi (Full Professional)

Punjabi (Native or Bilingual)

English (Full Professional)

#### Certifications

The Science of Well-Being
Viral Marketing and How to Craft
Contagious Content

#### Honors-Awards

Gladrags Miss India/Megamodel Runner Up

# Jaskirat Kaur

IIM Bangalore | IIT Bombay | Gladrags Miss India Pageant Winner Mumbai

## Summary

#### Features:

Times of India - https://tinyurl.com/tolu5vz Network Capital - https://tinyurl.com/s8h4vy5 Indian Express - https://tinyurl.com/togb2bn

An engineer from IIT turned Gladrags model. A marketing professional with a YouTube channel as a hobby. Currently, pursuing MBA at IIM Bangalore. I also enjoy modelling in print shoots, ads or short films. Coming from a small town to where I am today, the experiences have given me a driving force which I work towards - women empowerment by being an active member of 'Lean In' group by Sheryl Sandberg and bringing the youth of our nation forward in the big movements for the betterment of society with the help of 'Nation First'.

I have 2.5 years experience in marketing and content production in different industries which has given me a scope to understand the importance of different marketing strategies with different audience. I have been always lucky to be in touch with technical aspect of the marketing channels including the pre and post analysis of the content on different digital platforms including social media through Google Adwords, Google Keyword Planner, Google Trends, Vidooly etc.

Content marketing has always been an integral part of my digital marketing strategies as it helps in good SEO rankings and user engagement, through the use of prompt and positive communication, visual design, content strategies, apt image and presence in social media platforms, market research and making an effort to cater to the target audience's needs.

# Experience

Mahindra Group Strategy Intern March 2020 - May 2020 (3 months) Mumbai, Maharashtra

Nation First
Marketing (Socialist)
July 2018 - April 2019 (10 months)
Mumbai Area, India

Nation First is a non political and non- profit initiative started by renowned socialist like Mayank Gandhi. It ensures Public Charitable Trusts in India fulfil their commitments and obligations made to society, in lieu of the benefits that they have taken from our governments. Responsible for the marketing campaigns and awareness programmes especially promoting the involvement of women and youngsters towards big movements of our country like Nation First.

Kult Head Of Content January 2018 - June 2018 (6 months) Mumbai Area, India

Core Team member at Kult - Online beauty platform where you can buy all the cosmetic brands according to your skin type, textures etc at the lowest prices.

Games2win India Pvt Ltd Fashion Game Producer January 2017 - December 2017 (1 year) Mumbai Area, India

Conceptualising & designing fashion centric mobile based games for teens which are not just entertaining but a learning medium if they see themselves in this industry in future. Different products/games have been designed depending upon age group: early teens & late teens and country. e.g Games: International Fashion Stylist, Indian Fashion Stylist, Fashion Diva etc (All these games can be found on playstore) The apparels and outfits in the games are always upto the current and global trends. Responsible for the end to end delivery of each and every aspect of the game including art, content, ads etc.

glamrs.com Marketing Content Manager March 2016 - March 2017 (1 year 1 month) Style Editor & Business Developer

Director and producer of multiple style videos which would guide women to embrace their own style and make their own statement in the society. Content planning and execution across social media platforms had played an important part in promoting the style content.

Aasaanjobs.com
Marketing Manager
March 2015 - October 2015 (8 months)
Mumbai

P&L leadership of 5 associates to execute 2 offline marketing campaigns across channels: Print Media, OOH, Radio after the ROI & Impression-Retention analysis of various ideas for offline marketing.

Housing.com
Assistant Manager in Marketing
July 2014 - March 2015 (9 months)

Quality checked operational processes in listing of properties through surveys and in-depth interviews across country. Executed merchandise procurement and distribution of worth 34 lacs for brand launch for 1800 employees.

## Gladrags

Model

February 2013 - February 2014 (1 year 1 month)

Mumbai Area, India

2nd Runner Up of beauty pageant GLADRAGS MEGAMODEL & MANHUNT'13 from 25k models across India. Catalogue shoots, short films, ramps have been an important part of my journey as a freelance model since then.

## Education

Indian Institute of Management Bangalore

Master of Business Administration - MBA · (2019 - 2021)

Indian Institute of Technology, Bombay
Engineer's degree, Metallurgical and Material Science
Engineering · (2010 - 2014)

Nanyang Technological University

Internship, Global Technology Program · (2012 - 2012)